fakemailgenerator.com 2012-06-05

# FAQ - Fake Mail Generator

## FAQ

### What is the Fake Mail Generator?

The Fake Mail Generator is a website that allows you to circumvent email confirmations by giving you a one time email address to use. Next time a site asks for your email address, give them a Fake Mail Generator address and avoid the spam that is sure to follow. 

###  Why is it called the Fake Mail Generator?

This site is an extension of the [Fake Name Generator](http://www.fakenamegenerator.com/ "Fake Name Generator"), which generates fake names, addresses, and other information. The name of this site was chosen to match its parent site. 

### How does this site make money?

This site is entirely advertiser supported. 

### Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at jacob.allred@corbanworks.com.

At Fake Mail Generator, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Fake Mail Generator and how it is used.

#### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, Fake Mail Generator makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

Fake Mail Generator does use cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, record user-specific information on which pages users access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Fake Mail Generator.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to Fake Mail Generator and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

#### Advertising Partners

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

  * Google Adsense
  * Commission Junction
  * Clickbank
  * Chitika
  * Linkshare
  * Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use various technologies to show the advertisements and some links that appear on Fake Mail Generator. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Fake Mail Generator has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Fake Mail Generator's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
